SHRUTHI

Plot 5 flat no A4 Lakshmiganapathi Flats Lakshmi nagar madipakkam chennai 600091

Mobile: +91-9710922339

Email :shrunans@gmail.com

Summary:

Graduated in Commerce with 4.3 years experience in Finacial Market Operations and Eight months in Anti money Laundering

> Responsible for Nostro Investigations and Compensations.

Wide Knowledge in Foreign Exchange, Money Markets Operations. Encompass Compensations claims from various corporate and interbank Clients.

EXPERIENCE:

Worked in Scope International, Chennai as Senior Officer- Financial Markets operations from May 2010 to till 2013 December; Global Reconciliation Unit From Jan 2014 till Mar 2015 and as an Analyst in Anti money laundering from Mar 2015 till Oct2015

Job Responsibilities:

- **Investigations** Responsible for Nostro and Compensations.
- Responsibilities analyzing encompass and investigating of the Nostro outstandings.
- > Follow up with the client/remitter for non-receipt of funds Report and settle fail trade on daily basis Maintain MIS on the monthly basis Effective follow up with counter party for claims / compensations Analyze and settle penalties Reconciliation of Nostro charges across all the countries.
- > Won many Icon awards for nostro nil outstanding greater than 30 days as well for nil errors.
- > Project Management Report Preparation.

- ➤ Ensuring the bank performs the financial transactions and maintains the required documents and records in the manner as required by the law
- Analyzing extensive accounting statements to detect any patterns or trends that present illegal activities or frauds
- Preparing weekly/monthly reports on forensic investigation of departmental and organizational accounts. And handling a team wherein it's my responsibility for the day to day activities.
- ➤ Have been a functional coordinator and was responsibile for department functioning activities, priotising email request, communicate with vendor third parties follow up requests raising laptops and end to end functional activities.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:

COURSE	COLLEGE/SCHOOL	UNIVERSITY/BOARD	YEAR	% MARKS
B.Com	M.O.P Vaishnav College For women, Nungambakkam	Madras University	2007-10	70%
HSC	Asan Memorial Matriculation Higher Secondary School, Chennai	Tamil Nadu State Board	2007	87%
SSLC	Asan Memorial Senior Secondary School, Chennai	Central Board	2005	61%

<u>Languages</u> <u>known</u>	Speak: Tamil, English, Hindi, Gujarathi
	Read: Tamil, English, Hindi
	Write: Tamil, English, Hindi

APPLICATIONS USED:

- > TLM(RECONCILITATION)
- > PSGL(People Soft General Ledger)
- > OPICS GDC (all the deal flow)
- > SC STAR (Messaging system)
- > REUTERUS (Dealers Conversation)
- > CRYSTAL BUSINESS OBJECTS (Comp in reports)
- > CERS (Case log)
- > POSEWEB(compensation rates extraction)
- > GDC REPORTS (GL extracts)
- > FILE NET (Book transfers)
- > ICM(case log maintainance)
- > Detica

Joining date immediate Last designation: Analyst

PERSONAL INFORMATION:

NAME : Shruthi L
DATE OF BIRTH : 15/06/1990
SEX : Female

HUSBAND'S NAME : Lakshmi Narayanan V

NATIONALITY : Indian

0

PLACE: Chennai

DATE: 20-February-2019

(Shruthi)